Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Undated Material from Various Campaigns, 1800s-2000s
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David, 1950s
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-009)
    - Button with text: Let's Back Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-010)
    - Button with text: Let's Back Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-011)
    - Button with text: Let's Back Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-012)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-013)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-014)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-015)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-016)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-017)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-018)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-019)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-020)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-021)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-022)
    - Vari-vue button with image of Eisenhower and text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-023)
    - Vari-vue button with printed photograph of Eisenhower and text: I Like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-024)
    - Vari-vue button with printed photographs of Eisenhower and Nixon, and text: Peace Progress Prosperity: Ike / Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-025)
    - Button with text: Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-026)
    - Button with text: Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-027)
    - Litho tab with text: Ike & Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-028)
    - Litho tab with text: Ike-Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-029)
    - Litho tab with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-030)
    - Pin with deer and text: Young Bucks for Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-031)
    - Pin with deer and text: Young Bucks for Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-032)
    - Button with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-033)
    - Button with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-034)
    - Button with US map outline and text: US for Ike Vote Republican, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-035)
    - Litho tab with US map outline and text: US for Ike Vote Republican, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-036)
    - Button with printed photograph of Eisenhower and text: For President Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-037)
    - Button with printed photograph of Eisenhower and text: America Needs Ike/Ike Needs America, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-038)
    - Button with text: Ike and Nixon, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-039)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Eisenhower, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-040)
    - Button with text: Don't Ask., 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-041)
    - Button with printed photograph of Eisenhower and text: Peace and Prosperity with Eisenhower, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-042)
    - Pin with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-043)
    - Pin with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-044)
    - Pin with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-045)
    - Pin with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-046)
    - Button with text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-047)
    - Pin with US map outline and text: Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-048)
    - Button with text: Let's Clean House with Ike and Dick, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-049)
    - Button with text: I like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-050)
    - Button with text: I like Ike, 1952 or 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE19xx-051)
  - Kefauver, Carey Estes, 1950s
    - Button with text: Elect Kefauver President, 1952 or 1956 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-CEK19xx-001)
    - Button with text: Elect Kefauver President, 1952 or 1956 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-CEK19xx-002)
    - Button with text: Elect Kefauver President, 1952 or 1956 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-CEK19xx-003)
  - Stevenson, Adlai Ewing, 1950s
    - Lenticular button with photograph of Stevenson and text: All the way with Adlai, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-001)
    - Button with printed photograph of Stevenson and text: For President Adlai E. Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-002)
    - Button with printed photograph of Stevenson and text: For President Adlai E. Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-003)
    - Litho tab with donkey and text: All the way with Adlai, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-004)
    - Button with printed photograph of Stevenson and text: Forward with Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-005)
    - Button with printed photograph of Stevenson and text: Our Next President Adlai Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-006)
    - Button with text: Labor Supports Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-007)
    - Button with text: Labor Supports Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-008)
    - Button with text: Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-009)
    - Button with text: Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-010)
    - Button with text: Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-011)
    - Button with text: Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-012)
    - Button with text: Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-013)
    - Button with text: Stevenson, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-014)
    - Cigarette carton with printed photograph of Stevenson and text: Stephenson for President, 1952, 1956, or 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES19xx-015)
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1960s
    - Button with text: I'm for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-001)
    - Button with text: I'm for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-002)
    - Button with text: I'm for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-003)
    - Button with text: I'm for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-004)
    - Button with text: Nixon's the One!, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-005)
    - Button with text: Nixon's the One!, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-006)
    - Lenticular pin with printed photograph of Nixon and text: I'm for Nixon!, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-007)
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: Nixon's the One! Nixon's the One!, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-008)
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: Nixon's the One!, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-009)
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: Nixon for President, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-010)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-011)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-012)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-013)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-014)
    - Button with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-015)
    - Button with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-016)
    - Button with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-017)
    - Pin shaped like elephant with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-018)
    - Pin shaped like elephant with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-019)
    - Pin shaped like elephant with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-020)
    - Beaded pin shaped like elephant with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-021)
    - Beaded pin with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-022)
    - Beaded pin with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-023)
    - Pin shaped like flag with text: The Nation for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-024)
    - Pin shaped like flag with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-025)
    - Button with text: Nixon Now, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-026)
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: I'm for Dick Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-027)
    - Pin with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-028)
    - Pin with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-029)
    - Pin with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-030)
    - Litho tab with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-031)
    - Litho tab with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-032)
    - Litho tab with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-033)
    - Button with text: Nixon's for Farmers, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-034)
    - Button with text: Maritime Citizens for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-035)
    - Button with text: Another Democrat for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-036)
    - Button with drawing of Nixon's head, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-037)
    - Pin with text: N, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-038)
    - Tie clasp with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-039)
    - Button with text: Another Democrat for Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-040)
    - Pin shaped like elephant with text: Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-041)
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: I'm for Dick Nixon, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-042)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-043)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-044)
    - Pin with text: N/A, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-045)
    - Button with text: Women for Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-046)
    - Button with text: I'm for Milhous, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-047)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-048)
    - Button with text: Nixon Agnew, 1968 or 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN19xx-049)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich, 1960s
    - Button with text: Draft Rockefeller, 1960, 1964, or 1968 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-NAR19xx-001)
    - Button with text: Rocky!, 1960, 1964, or 1968 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-NAR19xx-002)
    - Button with text: Rocky!, 1960, 1964, or 1968 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-NAR19xx-003)
    - Button with text: Citizens for Rockefeller, 1960, 1964, or 1968 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-NAR19xx-004)
    - Button with text: Win with Rockefeller for President, 1960, 1964, or 1968 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-NAR19xx-005)
  - Sanford, James Terry, 1970s
    - Button with text: Sanford for President, 1972 or 1976 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-JTS19xx-001)
  - Bush, George Herbert Walker, 1980s
    - Pin and accompanying thank-you note for supporting the Bush campaign, 1988 or 1992 (Box 16)
  - Reagan, Ronald Wilson, 1980s
    - Button with text: The time is now. Reagan Bush, 1980 or 1984 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-RWR19xx-001)
    - Button blue with text: Reagan. Let's make America great again, 1980 or 1984 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-RWR19xx-002)
    - Button with text: The time is now. Reagan Bush, 1980 or 1984 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-RWR19xx-003)
  - Clinton, William Jefferson, 1990s
    - Button shaped like a heart with printed photograph of Hillary Clinton, 1992 or 1996 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-WJC19xx-001)
    - Button with text: Pro Family Pro Choice Pro Clinton, 1992 or 1996 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-WJC19xx-002)
    - Tie with caricatures of former presidents and Clinton playing saxophone, 1992 or 1996 (Box 18, Item RL-00580-WJC19xx-003)
  - Bush, George W., 2000s
    - Button with printed color photograph of Bush and text: George W. Bush for President, 2000 or 2004 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GWB20xx-001)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Bush and text: George W. Bush for President, 2000 or 2004 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GWB20xx-002)
    - Pin with star and text: George W. Bush USA President, 2000 or 2004 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GWB20xx-003)
    - Pin with text: Bush Cheney, 2000 or 2004 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-GWB20xx-004)
  - Obama, Barack Hussein, 2000s
    - Button with text: Vote Obama, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-001)
    - Button with text: Vote for Obama, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-002)
    - Button with printed photograph of Obama, a copy of Obama's birth certificate and text: Made in the USA, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-003)
    - Button with O graphic, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-004)
    - Button with printed photograph of Obama, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-005)
    - Button with printed photograph of Obama and text: Barack Obama for President, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-006)
    - Button with text: Obama Biden, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-007)
    - Button with text: Obama Biden, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-008)
    - Button with printed photograph of Joe and Jill Biden, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-009)
    - Button with printed photograph of Obama and Biden, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-010)
    - Button with printed photograph of Biden, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-011)
    - Button with text: Our Health Our Vote Women for Obama, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-012)
    - Button with text: !Obama!, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-013)
    - Button with text: !Obama!, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-014)
    - Button with printed color photograph of Obama and his family with text: Obama Biden, 2008 or 2012 (Box 11, Item RL-00580-BHO20xx-015)